zerodollartips.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Zero Dollar Tips - Android and Windows 10 Tutorials

[__  Home](https://www.zerodollartips.com/) > Privacy Policy

At [Zero Dollar Tips](https://www.zerodollartips.com/about-us/ "Zero Dollar Tips") the privacy of our readers/visitors is exceedingly important. This Privacy Policy outlines the all types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

Our privacy policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will wish to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

Here is the detailed acquaintance on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use or visit Zerodollartips.com, and how we safeguard your information.

## Log Files

In accordance with the Google Adsense Terms of Service, we are required to let you know that all advertising programs use cookies to track visitors. We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include: IP (Internet Protocol) addresses, your ISP (airtel, bsnl, mtnl, tata etc….), types of browser you used to visit our site, date and time stamp, referring and exit pages, number of clicks. All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies

We do use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, Zerodollartips.com has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

In case, if you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

### Email Addresses

When you make a comment on blog post or contact us using the contact page your email is required. Please be assured that your email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available.

> “We never sell your personal information to third parties”

### Comments Policy

The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are always welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed!

> “Spam in any form will not be accepted”

### Copyrights

You are not supposed to re publish any contents from ZeroDollarTips.com without our permission. If you want to publish any part of articles on print media or other websites, you must get permission before doing so.

Zero Dollar Tips team take plagiarism very seriously. If we discover that any website/blog republishing our Articles or RSS feeds without our permission, we will take some quick actions and file a formal DMCA complaint with their advertising partners and also with the hosting company.

Publishing or copying articles from ZeroDollarTips.com in any other form is not allowed.

### Contacting Us

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please……. feel free to contact us by email at **zerodollartips@gmail.com** or use our [Contact Us](https://www.zerodollartips.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") form.
